goemerchant.com 2008-06-16

# Privacy Statement - GoEmerchant.com

**GoEmerchant Information Security and Privacy Statement**  
This statement provides you with information regarding the policies we have established and follow by which we protect the privacy and integrity of the information we collect. 

**This statement describes:**  

**Information We Collect**  
GoEmerchant provides services that enhance the procurement of goods and services, and the payment and collection of payments by commercial and non-commercial enterprises. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed within this statement and within any agreements with our customers.

Our customers are business or other non-person legal entities. Therefore, most of the information we receive and collect is not of a personal nature. However, portions of the information we receive from our business customers may include public and non-public information about our customers, persons, and businesses.

Regardless of the nature of the information and regardless of whether it is information we solicit directly from our customers, from visitors to our Web site or whether we collect the information during the processing of visiting one of our sites, we regard all such information as private and take steps to protect the integrity and confidentiality of the information.

**Commitment to Security, Privacy, and Standards**  
GoEmerchant takes seriously our responsibility to protect the security and privacy of the information we receive and maintain. We have established effective policies as defined by Visa CISP and Mastercard SDP that define our commitment to protecting the information and information technology we administer. We continue to review our policies and procedures to assure that they are appropriate and effective in meeting our commitments to our community, our customers, and ourselves.

Any suspected attempt to breach these policies and procedures or to engage in any type of unauthorized action involving this Web site is regarded as potential criminal activity and all suspected computer mischief is reported to the appropriate authorities.

**GoEmerchant Use of Personal Information**  
Information collected regarding visitors to our Web site will be used by GoEmerchant only as appropriate to provide authorized services or to communicate information regarding GoEmerchant services. No information regarding specific persons, including our customers, our employees, or visitors to our Web site, will be provided to any non-affiliated organization, except as may be legally required, to prevent fraud, or to comply with the legal inquiry of the government. This policy does not preclude GoEmerchant unrestricted use of non-personal, summarized, derived, or aggregate information (i.e., volumes, totals, averages, etc.).

**Customer Options**  
GoEmerchant does not anticipate a change in its policies regarding the use of personal information (see section above, Use of Personal Information). However, should GoEmerchant at some future time, change its practices regarding the use of personal information (i.e., to share such information with third parties) our customers will be provided an opportunity to choose to be excluded from any such use of public or non-public personal information prior to their information being used for such purposes. You have a choice, where and what you want to be viewed, and you have the option of providing your personal information to our Web Site and link sites.

**Changes to Information Security and Privacy Statement**  
GoEmerchant continues to adhere to good business practices. We will regularly review our policies and practices as it determines them to be warranted. When changes are made that affect the GoEmerchant Information Security and Privacy Statement, these changes will be posted to our Web site.

**Information Collected via Our Web Site**  
We solicit, collect, or retain public or non-public personal information regarding customers or visitors to our Internet sites, only as may be required to allow GoEmerchant to respond to requests for information about our products and services. The only information obtained about a visitor to its Web site is information that is voluntarily supplied by that visitor. Information about our customers and visitors to our Web sites, regardless of whether acquired via our Web site, or through other means, is not shared with affiliated or non-affiliated entities.

**Cookies**  
GoEmerchant site(s) may create a file or cookie on the hard drive of your computer in order to retain information that is used by our Web site. These files are used during your online session to ensure access to our site is authorized and to control certain parameters of your communication session with our site. We do not use these files to monitor the behavior of visitors to our sites. Sponsors and advertisers may also use cookies if you choose to visit their advertisement. Information regarding their use of cookies should be obtained directly from those providers.

**IP Addresses**  
An IP address is a number assigned to your computer for accessing the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted using IP addresses, to allow other computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. If a visitor requests pages from the GoEmerchant site(s) or our affiliate site(s), the servers enter the visitor's IP address into a log. We do not associate IP addresses with personal information received from visitors.

**External Links**  
GoEmerchant may provide links on the Web site, via advertising and otherwise, to other web sites that are not under our control. We do not endorse or make any warranty of any type regarding the content contained on such web sites or products and services offered therein. GoEmerchant makes no representation regarding your use of such web sites. 

Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by these Web sites.

**Children**  
We do not provide content on our Web sites which are intended to attract or encourage the participation of children. We do not solicit or knowingly accept information from persons under the age of 18.

**Your Responsibility**  
As a customer/merchant to one of our web sites, you may be provided with a unique identifier such as a password, or pin number which is intended to authenticate your identity when accessing our systems. Such identifying items are intended to be secret and to be known, possessed, and used only by you. The effectiveness of these mechanisms for authenticating your identity are dependent upon your keeping them in your exclusive possession and upon your protecting them from the discovery, access, possession of others. If you fail to keep such identifying information in your exclusive possession (i.e., you allow others to have knowledge or possession of your password or pin), you may bear responsibility for the actions of other persons who use this information in accessing our systems. If your personal identifier, pin number, has been lost or disclosed to someone other than yourself, you should immediately contact one of our sites or customer service.

**Questions.**

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please send an e-mail to [sales@goEmerchant.com](mailto:sales@goEmerchant.com).

**Call 1-888-638-7867 or[Apply Online](https://www.goemerchant.com/cgi-bin/goeapp.cgi?page=Profile) Today

Our Total Package is ONLY $59.95/month

**  
(Plus merchant account fees)
